Guide to the Robert O. Pohl papers, 1973-1998
Pohl, Robert O. papers, 1973-1998
- Series II. Published Reports on Nuclear Waste
  - Information Base for Waste Repository Design, March 1979 (Box 16)
    - Vol. 3: Waste/Rock Interactions (Box 16)
    - Vol. 4: Mine Structural Features (Box 16)
    - Vol. 5: Decommissioning of Underground Facilities (Box 16)
    - Vol. 6: Excavation Technology (Box 16)
    - Vol. 7: Executive Summary (Box 16)
  - Alternate Nuclear Waste Forms and Interactions in Geologic Media: Proceedings of a Workshop Summarizing Advanced Activities and Formulating Requirements for the Future, May 13-15, 1980 (Box 16)
  - Public Draft: National Plan for Siting High-Level Radioactive Waste Repositories and Environmental Assessment, February 1982 (Box 16)
  - Evaluation of Geotechnical Surveillance Techniques for Monitoring High-Level Waste Repository Performance, Final Report, September 1980 - December 1981 (Box 16)
  - U.S. Department of Energy, Notice of Public Hearing and Solicitation of Comments: Nuclear Waste Policy Act of 1982 (Box 16)
  - A National Survey of Crystalline Rocks and Recommendations of Regions to be Explored for High-Level Radioactive Waste Repository Sites, April 1983 (Box 16)
  - Expected Repository Environments in Granite: Thermal Environment, October 1984 (Box 16)
  - Interim Rock Mass Properties and Conditions for Analyses of a Repository in Crystalline Rock, March 1985 (Box 16)
  - Expected Brine Movement at Potential Nuclear Waste Repository Salt Sites, August 1987 (Box 16)
  - Expected Near-Field Radionuclide Transport for Nuclear Waste Repositories at Potential Salt Sites, November 1987 (Box 16)
  - Office of Civilian Radioactive Waste Management: Annual Report to Congress, December 1989 (Box 16)
  - Progress Report on the Scientific Investigation Program for the Nevada Yucca Mountain Site, February 1990 (Box 16)
  - Transport of Soluble Species in Backfill and Rock, March 1992 (Box 16)
  - Radioactive Waste Forms for the Future, Chapter 3, Lead-Iron Phosphate Glass, 1988 (Box 16)
  - Radioactive Waste Forms for the Future, Chapter 8, Monazite, 1988 (Box 16)
  - Design and Implementation of a DC- Based Magnetic Field Controller with Electronic Temperature Stabilized Hall Generator, July 1992 (Box 16)
  - Characteristics of Potential Repository Wastes Vol. 1-4, July 1992 (Box 16)
  - Polyethylene Encapsulation of Single- Shell Tank Low-Level Wastes: Annual Progress Report, September 1992 (Box 16)
  - Remote Purge and Trap of Volatile Organic Compounds in High Level Radioactive Wastes at the Idaho Chemical Processing Plant, September 1992 (Box 16)
  - Strategy for OCRWM to Provide Training Assistance to State, Tribal, and Local Governments, November 1992 (Box 16)
  - Dynamic Soil Pressures on Rigid Vertical Walls, December 1992 (Box 16)
  - ICPP Waste Management Technology Development Program, January 1993 (Box 16)
  - The Use of a Centrifugal Contactor for Component Concentration by Solvent Extraction (Box 16)
  - Spent Nuclear Fuel Storage - Performance Tests and Demonstrations, April 1993 (Box 16)
  - Preliminary Assessment of Real-Time Radiography and Visual Characterization for Selected Waste Categories, October 22, 1993 (Box 16)
  - United States Nuclear Regulatory Commission: Memo. re LWR Occupational Dose Data for 1992, November 22, 1993 (Box 16)
  - Evaluation of Residue Drum Storage Safety Risks, June 17, 1994 (Box 16)
  - OCWRM Bulletin: Multi-Purpose Canister Procurement: a Significant Step for the Department of Energy's Civilian Radioactive Waste Management Program, August 1994 (Box 16)
  - Molten Salt Oxidation of Mixed Wastes: Preliminary Bench-Scale Experiments without Radioactivity (Box 16)
  - Nuclear Energy Insight: Energy Security: Experts Cite Nuclear's Appeal, October 1996 (Box 16)
  - Methods for Removing Transuranic Elements from Waste Solutions (Box 16)
  - Process Description and Plant Design for Preparing Ceramic High-Level Waste Forms (Box 16)
  - Development of Polyphase Ceramics for the Immobilization of High-Level Defense Nuclear Waste (Box 16)
  - A Preliminary Assessment of Mineralogical Criteria on the Utility of Argillaceous Rocks and Minerals for High-Level Radioactive Waste Disposal (Box 16)
  - Partitioning High-Level Waste from Alkaline Solution: A Literature Survey (Box 16)
  - The OCRWM Enterprise, December 1996 (Box 16)
  - Institut Fur Tieflagerung Wissenschaftliche Abteilung Zur Standsicherheit des Salzbergwerkes Asse II als Endlager fur radioactive Abfalle, January 1974 (Box 17)
  - Release of Radon Contaminants from Yucca Mountain: The Role of Buoyancy Driven Flow, February 1994 (Box 17)
  - OCRWM Bulletin, Summer/Fall 1994 (Box 17)
  - Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project Bibliography, January-June 1994, An Update, January 1995 (Box 17)
  - Site Characterization Progress Report: Yucca Mountain, Nevada, April 1997 (Box 17)
  - Technical and Administrative Approach for the West Valley Demonstration Project Safety Program, June1987 (Box 17)
  - Decontamination of the Scrap Removal Room at the West Valley Demonstration Plant, February 1987 (Box 17)
  - Brine Migration Test for Asse Mine, Federal Republic of Germany: Final Design Report, August 1987 (Box 17)
  - Annual Technology Assessment and Progress Report for the Buried Transuranic Waste Studies Program at the Idaho National Engineering Laboratory (1987), January 1988 (Box 17)
  - Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project Bibliography 1994-1995, August 1996 (Box 17)
  - Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project Bibliography, January-June 1995, An Update, January 1996 (Box 17)
  - OCRWM Bulletin, Fall 1995 (Box 17)
  - Nevada Nuclear Waste Storage Investigations, January-June 1987, An Update, March 1988 (Box 17)
  - Development of the Open Items Tracking System, June 1, 1994 (Box 17)
  - Low-level Liquid Waste Treatment System Start-up, July 1989 (Box 17)
  - High-level Waste Tank Modifications, Installation of Mobilization Equipment/Check out, August 31, 1992 (Box 17)
  - The Crystallization Behavior of the West Valley Reference Borosilicate Glass, April 1988 (Box 17)
  - West Valley Demonstration Project Vitrification Process Equipment Functional and Checkout Testing of Systems (FACTS), September 30, 1990 (Box 17)
  - Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project Bibliography 1992-1993, August 1994 (Box 17)
  - Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project Bibliography, July-December 1994, An Update, July 1995 (Box 17)
  - Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project Bibliography, January-June 1992, An Update, October 1992 (Box 17)
  - Glass Mixing Theory and Tracer Study Results From the SF-10 Run, August 1988 (Box 17)
  - The Influence of Waste Variability on the Properties and Phase Stability of the West Valley Reference Glass, September 1987 (Box 17)
  - Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project Bibliography, January-June 1993, An Update, November 1993 (Box 17)
  - Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project Bibliography, July-December 1992, An Update, April 1993 (Box 17)
  - Functional Description of the West Valley Demonstration Project Vitrification Facility, July 1990 (Box 17)
  - Design Characteristics of the Sludge Mobilization System, September 30, 1990 (Box 17)
  - The Integrated Melter Off-Gas Treatment Systems at the West Valley Demonstration Project, December 1991 (Box 17)
  - Technical Concept for a Test of Geologic Storage of Spent Reactor Fuel in the Climax Granite, Nevada Test Site, June 15, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Yucca Mountain Site Characterization Project Bibliography, 1990-1991, June 1992 (Box 17)
  - Swedish-American Cooperative Program on Radioactive Waste Storage in Mined Caverns in Crystalline Rock: A Pilot Heater Test in the Stripa Granite, August 1978 (Box 17)
  - OCRWM Bulletin, Winter 1996 (Box 17)
  - OCRWM Bulletin, Summer 1995 (Box 17)
  - Die Untertage-Deponie Herfa-Neurode bei Heringen/Werra (Box 17)
  - Project Salt Vault: A Demonstration of Disposal of High-Activity Solidified Wastes in Underground Salt Mines, April 1971 (Box 17)
  - Final Supplement Environmental Impact Statement: Waste Isolation Pilot Plant, Executive Summary, January 1990 (Box 17)
  - Reference Site Initial Assessment for a Salt Dome Repository Vol. 1-2, December, 1979 (Box 17)
  - Proceedings: A Workshop on Issues Pertinent to the Development of Environmental Protection Criteria for Radioactive Wastes, February 3-5, 1977 (Box 18)
  - Proceedings: A Workshop on Policy and Technical Issues Pertinent to the Development of Environmental Protection Criteria for a Radioactive Wastes, April 12-14, 1977 (Box 18)
  - High-level Radioactive Waste from Light-Water Reactors, January 1977 (Box 18)
  - Working Level Screening Survey of Structures Constructed of Materials Containing Pumice, May 1978 (Box 18)
  - Correlation of Radioactive Waste Treatment Costs and the Environmental Impact of Waste Effluents in the Nuclear Fuel Cycle for Use in Establishing "As Low as Practicable" Guides-Milling of Uranium Ores Vol. 1-2, May 1975 (Box 18)
  - Potential Radiological Impacts of Recovery of Uranium from Wet-Process Phosphoric Acid, January 1979 (Box 18)
  - Review and Recommendations of Dose Conversion Factors and Environmental Transport Parameters for 210Pb and 226Ra, Final Report, March 1979 (Box 18)
  - Environmental Analysis of the Uranium Fuel Cycle, October-November 1973 (Box 18)
    - Part I - Fuel Supply (Box 18)
    - Part II - Nuclear Power Reactors (Box 18)
    - Part III - Nuclear Fuel Reprocessing (Box 18)
    - Part IV - Supplementary Analysis, 1976 (Box 18)
  - Description of the Formerly Utilized Sites Remedial Action Program, September 1980 (Box 18)
  - Development of Plan & Approach for Borehole Plugging Field Testing, October 1978 (Box 18)
  - Formerly Utilized Sites: Remedial Action, November 1982, April 1985 (Box 18)
  - Radiological survey of the Former Kellex Research Facility, Jersey City, New Jersey, February 1982 (Box 18)
  - Radiological Survey of the Mallinckrodt Chemical Works, St. Louis, Missouri, December 1981 (Box 18)
  - Radiological Survey of the Former Bridgeport Brass Company Special Metals Extrusion Plant, Adrian, Michigan, April 1982 (Box 18)
  - Formerly Utilized MED/AEC Sites Remedial Action Program: Radiological Survey of the Middlesex Sampling Plant, Middlesex, New Jersey, Final Report, November 1977 (Box 18)
  - Formerly Utilized MED/AEC Sites Remedial Action Program: Radiological Survey of the Seaway Industrial Park, Tonawanda, New York, Final Report, May 1978 (Box 18)
  - Formerly Utilized MED/AEC Sites Remedial Action Program: Radiological Survey of the Hooker Chemical Company, Niagara Falls, New York, Final Report, January 1977 (Box 18)
  - Formerly Utilized MED/AEC Sites Remedial Action Program: Radiological Survey of the Former Linde Uranium Refinery, Tonawanda, New York, Final Report, May 1978 (Box 18)
  - Formerly Utilized MED/AEC Sites Remedial Action Program: Radiological Survey of the Middlesex Municipal Landfill, Middlesex, New Jersey, Final Report, April 1980 (Box 18)
  - Formerly Utilized MED/AEC Sites Remedial Action Program: Radiological Survey of Site A, Palos Park Forest Preserve, Chicago, Illinois, Final Report, April 1978 (Box 18)
  - Formerly Utilized MED/AEC Sites Remedial Action Program: Radiological Survey of the Former VITRO Rare Metals Plant, Canonsburg, Pennsylvania, Interim Report, April 1978 (Box 18)
  - Formerly Utilized MED/AEC Sites Remedial Action Program: Radiological Survey of the Building Site 421, United States Watertown Arsenel, Watertown, MA, Final Report, February 1980 (Box 18)
  - Development Document for Interim Final Effluent Limitations Guidelines and New Source Performance Standards for the Minerals for the Chemical and Fertilizer Industries, Vol. II, October 1975 (Box 18)
  - Technology, Safety and Costs of Decommissioning a Reference Pressurized Water Reactor Power Station Vol. 1 Vol. 2: Appendices Addendum, June 1978, August 1979 (Box 19)
  - Decommissioning of Nuclear Facilities- An Annotated Bibliography, October 1978 (Box 19)
  - Long-Lived Activation Products in Reactor Materials, August 1984 (Box 19)
  - Decommissioning Handbook, November 1980 (Box 19)
  - Evaluation of Nuclear Facility Decommissioning Projects: Summary Status Report, Three Mile Island Unit 2, May 1986, June 1988 (Box 19)
    - Vol. 1: Reactor Coolant System and Systems Decontamination (Box 19)
    - Vol. 2: Reactor Building Decontamination (Box 19)
    - Vol. 3: Reactor Defueling and Disassembly (Box 19)
    - Vol. 9: Radioactive Waste and Laundry Shipments (Box 19)
  - An Engineering Evaluation of Nuclear Power Reactor Decommissioning Alternatives, November 1976 (Box 19)
  - Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement on decommissioning of nuclear facilities, August 1988 (Box 19)
  - Decontamination and Decommissioning, February 1985 (Box 19)
  - Technology, Safety and Costs of Decommissioning Reference Nuclear Research and Test Reactors, Sensitivity of Decommissioning Radiation, Exposure and Costs to Selected Parameters, July 1983 (Box 19)
  - Evaluation of Nuclear Facility Decommissioning Projects: Summary Report, Ames Laboratory Research Reactor, July 1983 (Box 19)
  - Evaluation of Nuclear Facility Decommissioning Projects: Summary Report, Enrico Fermi-1 Reactor, February 1983 (Box 19)
  - Technology, Safety and Costs of Decommissioning Reference Light Water Reactors Following Postulated Accidents Vol. 1-2, November 1982 (Box 19)
  - Decommissioning the los Alamos Molten Plutonium Reactor Experiment (LAMPRE I), November 1981 (Box 19)
  - The Decommissioning of a Tritium Contaminated Laboratory, November 1981 (Box 19)
  - Costs of Closing the Indian Point Nuclear Power Plant, November 1981 (Box 19)
  - Facilitation of Decommissioning Light Water Reactors, December 1979 (Box 19)
  - Plan for Reevaluation of NRC Policy on Decommissioning of Nuclear Facilities, March 1981 (Box 19)
  - Decommissioning of the Shippingport Atomic Power Station, May 1982 (Box 19)
  - Technology, Safety and Costs of Decommissioning Reference Non-Fuel- Cycle Nuclear Facilities, February 1981 (Box 19)
  - Evaluation of Nuclear Facility Decommissioning Projects, Project Summary Report, Elk River Reactor, December 1982 (Box 19)
  - Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement on decommissioning of nuclear facilities, January 1981 (Box 19)
  - Technology, Safety and Costs of Decommissioning a Reference Boiling Water Reactor Power Station Main Report, June 1980 (Box 19)
    - Vol. 1: Main Report (Box 19)
    - Vol. 2: Appendices (Box 19)
  - UNSCEAR, 24th Session, 1969 (Box 20)
  - The Effects on Populations of Exposure to Low Levels of Ionizing Radiation, November 1972 (Box 20)
  - International Symposium on Occupational Radiation Exposure in Nuclear Fuel Cycle Facilities, June 18-22, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Review and Assessment of Package Requirements (Yellowcake) and Emergency Response to Transportation Accidents, July 1980 (Box 20)
  - Reactor Safety Study: An Assessment of Accident Risks in U.S. Commercial Nuclear Power Plants, October 1975
    - Main Report (Box 20)
    - Appendix I: Accident Definition and Use of Event Trees (Box 20)
    - Appendix II: Fault Trees (Box 20)
    - Appendix III: Failure Data (Box 20)
    - Appendix IV: Common Mode Failures: Bounding Techniques and Special Techniques (Box 20)
    - Appendix V: Quantitative Results of Accident Sequences (Box 20)
    - Appendix VI: Calculations of Reactor Accident Consequences (Box 20)
    - Appendix VII: Release of Radioactivity in Reactor Accidents (Box 20)
    - Appendix VIII: Physical Processes in Reactor Meltdown Accidents (Box 20)
    - Appendix IX: Safety Design Rationale for Nuclear Power Plants (Box 20)
    - Appendix X: Design Adequacy (Box 20)
    - Appendix XI: Responses to Comments on Wash 1400 Draft Executive Summary (Box 20)
  - Betriebserfahrungen Mit Kernkraftwerken, January 1976 (Box 20)
  - Occupational Radiation Exposure, Eleventh Annual Report 1978, January 1981 (Box 20)
  - Considerations of Environmental Protection Criteria for Radioactive Waste, February 1978 (Box 20)
  - Occupational Radiation Exposure at Commercial Nuclear Power Reactors 1978, November 1979 (Box 20)
  - Occupational Radiation Exposure at Light Water Cooled Power Reactors 1976, March 1978 (Box 20)
  - Occupational Radiation Exposure at Light Water Cooled Power Reactors, Annual Report 1977, May 1979 (Box 20)
  - LWR Occupational Dose Data for 1995 (Box 20)
  - LWR Occupational Dose Data for 1993 (Box 20)
  - Environmental Survey of the Reprocessing and Waste Management Portions of the LWR Fuel Cycle, A Task Force Report, October 1976 (Box 20)
  - The Environmental Survey of the Reprocessing and Waste Management Portions of the LWR Fuel Cycle, March 1977 (Box 20)
  - State Background Radiation Levels: Results of Measurements Taken During 1975-1979, November 1981 (Box 20)
  - Environmental Survey of the Uranium Fuel Cycle, April 1974 (Box 20)
  - Age-Specific Radiation Dose Commitment Factors for a One-Year Chronic Intake, November 1977 (Box 20)
  - Waste Disposal Practices-A Threat to Health and the Nation's Water Supply, June 16, 1978 (Box 20)
  - Hazardous Waste Management Programs Will Not Be Effective: Greater Efforts Are Needed, January 23, 1979 (Box 20)
  - Estimate of the Cancer Risk Due to Nuclear-Electric Power Generation, October 1976 (Box 20)
  - Ionizing Radiation: Levels and Effects Vol. I: Levels Vol. II: Effects, 1972 (Box 20)
  - Radiological Surveillance Study at the Haddam Neck PWR Nuclear Power Station, December 1974 (Box 20)
  - Radiological Surveillance Studies at a Pressurized Water Nuclear Power Reactor, August 1973 (Box 20)
  - Radiological Surveillance Studies at a Boiling Water Nuclear Power Reactor, October 1974 (Box 20)
  - Trends '93: A compendium of data on global change, September 1994 (Box 21)
  - Industrial Cogeneration-What It Is, How It Works, Its Potential, April 29, 1980 (Box 21)
  - The Case for Industrial Cogeneration: Benefits for the Nation and Potential in New Jersey, 1977 (Box 21)
  - Climate in Crisis: The Greenhouse Effect and What We Can Do, 1990 (Box 21)
  - Carbon Dioxide Effects Research and Assessment Program, Carbon Dioxide Research Progress Report, Fiscal Year 1979, April 1980 (Box 21)
  - Environmental Control Technology for Atmospheric Carbon Dioxide, Final Report, May 1980 (Box 21)
  - Carbon Dioxide Effects Research and Assessment Program, The Role of Organic Soils in the World Caron Cycle-Problem Analysis and Research Needs, May 7-8, 1979 (Box 21)
  - Carbon Dioxide Effects Research and Assessment Program, The Role of Temperate Zone Forests in the World Carbon Cycle-Problem Definition and Research Needs, May 7-8, 1979 (Box 21)
  - Carbon Dioxide Effects Research and Assessment Program, Workshop on the Global Effects of Carbon Dioxide from Fossil Fuels, May 1979 (Box 21)
  - A Comprehensive Plan for Carbon Dioxide Effects Research and Assessment, Part I: The Global Carbon Cycle and Climatic Effects of Increasing Carbon Dioxide, May 1978 (Box 21)
  - Report of the Cornell Workshops on the Major Issues of a National Energy Research and Development Program, September 14-October 17, 1973 (Box 21)
  - Physical Properties Data for Rock Salt, January 1981 (Box 21)
  - Storage and Release of Radiation Energy in Salt in Radioactive Waste Repositories, October 1977 (Box 21)
  - Salt Deposits in the United States and Regional Geologic Characteristics Important for Storage of Radioactive Waste, March 1978 (Box 21)
  - Expected Near-Field Thermal Environments in a Sequentially Loaded Spent-Fuel or High-Level Waste Repository in Salt, January 1982 (Box 21)
  - Thermal Conductivity, Bulk Properties, and Thermal Stratigraphy of Silicic Tuffs From the Upper Portion of Hole USW-G1, Yucca Mountain, Nye County, Nevada, March 1982 (Box 21)
  - Effect of Pressure and Saturating Fluid on the Thermal Conductivity of Compact Rock, June 15, 1966 (Box 21)
  - Thermal Conductivity of Polyhalite and Anhydrite from the Site of the Proposed Waste Isolation Pilot Plant, March 1981 (Box 21)
  - Thermal Conductivity of Rocksalt and Other Geologic Materials from the Site of the Proposed Waste Isolation Pilot Plant, March 19, 1980 (Box 21)
  - Waste Package Heat-Transfer Analysis: Model Development and Temperature Estimates for Waste Packages in a Repository Located in Basalt, October 1981 (Box 21)
  - Thermal Properties of Climax Stock Quartz Monzonite to 523 K and 50-Mpa Confining Pressure, October 19, 1982 (Box 21)
  - Thermal Conductivity and Diffusivity of Permian Basin Bedded Salt at Elevated Pressure and Temperature, October 1983 (Box 21)
  - Bundesanstalt fur Geowissenschaften und Rohstoffe, May 1978 (Box 21)
  - Thermal Property and Density Measurements of Samples Taken From Drilling Cores From Potential Geologic Media, Technical Report, December 1983 (Box 21)
  - Thermal Conductivity of the Rocks in the Bureau of Mines Standard Rock Suite, January 1980 (Box 21)
  - Experimental and Analytical Studies of the Thermal Aspects of Deep Geologic Disposal of Commercial Nuclear Wastes, Technical Report, November 1987 (Box 21)
  - Uranium Mill Tailings, March 1985 (Box 22)
  - Annual Status Report on the Uranium Mill Tailings Remedial Action Program, December 1985 (Box 22)
  - Annual Status Report on the Uranium Mill Tailings Remedial Action Program, December 1984 (Box 22)
  - Progress Report on the Grand Junction Uranium Mill Tailings Remedial Action Program, February 1979 (Box 22)
  - Draft Generic Environmental Impact Statement on Uranium Milling Vol. 1: Summary and Text Vol. 2: Appendices, April 1979 (Box 22)
  - Isolation of Uranium Mill Tailings and Their Component Radionuclides From the Biosphere-Some Earth Science Perspectives, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Estimated Population Near Uranium Tailings, January 1984 (Box 22)
  - Potential Radiological Impact of Airborne Releases and Direct Gamma Radiation to Individuals Living Near Inactive Uranium Mill Tailings Piles, January 1976 (Box 22)
  - Final Environmental Impact Statement for Remedial Action Standards for Inactive Uranium Processing Sites (40 CFR 192) Vol. I-II, October 1982 (Box 22)
  - Annual Status Report on the Uranium Mill Tailings Remedial Action Program, December 1983 (Box 22)
  - Population Risks From Uranium Ore Bodies, October 1980 (Box 22)
  - Long Term Stabilization of Uranium Mill Tailings at Inactive Sites (Box 22)
  - Calculational Models for Estimating Radiation Doses to Man From Airborne Radioactive Materials Resulting From Uranium Milling Operations, March 1982 (Box 22)
  - Radium-226 Measurements Below Uranium Mill Tailings Piles, June 1982 (Box 22)
  - A Radiological Assessment of Radon-222 Released From Uranium Mills and Other Natural and Technologically Enhanced Sources, Final Report, February 1979 (Box 22)
  - Final Generic Environmental Impact Statement on uranium milling, Summary and Text, September 1980 (Box 22)
  - Draft Environmental Impact Statement for Standards for the Control of Byproduct Materials from Uranium Ore Processing (40 CFR 192), March 1983 (Box 22)
  - Final Environmental Impact Statement for Standards for the control of Byproduct Materials from Uranium Ore Processing (40 CFR 192) Vol. I-II, September 1983 (Box 22)
  - Management of Commingled Uranium Mill Tailings, August 19-18, 1982 (Box 22)
  - The Atomic Establishment (Box 22)
  - Radon Releases from Uranium Mining and Milling and their Calculated Health Effects, February 1981 (Box 22)
  - Federal Register, October 3, 1980 (Box 22)
  - Technical Assessment of Radon-222 Control Technology for Underground Uranium Mines, April 1980 (Box 22)
  - Kurz-Information, 1980 (Box 22)
  - RaDis sollen jetzt Radon messen, March 1981 (Box 22)
  - Uranium Mill Tailings, November 1982 (Box 22)
  - Federal Register, October 7, 1983 (Box 22)